Are you hurt?
Is it serious?
What did the doctor say?
I'm fine.
How are you?
Why did Lu Xu suddenly go crazy today?
I don't know.
I remember drinking water in the restaurant.
When I woke up, I was in Lu Xu's bed.
Are you his family?
His life was saved.
But he has Rh-negative blood,
so we need to
get blood from the blood bank.
And he
has multiple fractures
and severe concussion.
So he needs to be observed in ICU.
We can't estimate
when he will wake up.
I'll tell the Old Madam.
Tell everyone present today.
Whoever dares to tell my mother
will be put
in the ICU with Lu Xu.
Understand?
Yes.
I heard you got scratched by Lu Xu
while saving me.
What a pity.
It's on your face.
It doesn't matter.
Where are you going?
To get some air.
Jiang Li.
Today,
thank you.
[Hatred is blind.]
[Anger can make people lose their minds.]
[31.8 yuan has been paid.]
[Revenge]
[is meant to be the most beautiful tribute to the victim,]
[but it often burns itself up as well.]
I know that to gracefully exit the world's living room,
one must bow and depart.
But at this moment,
I have completely lost all means of retreat.
I live by revenge,
yet I am also being consumed by hatred.
I am prepared to endure the scorching flames of hell.
Because human justice
is nothing more than a clumsy imitation.
And I
will make it perfect.
Wounds in the rain
will get infected and scarred.
It might hurt a bit.
Bear with it for a while.
Does it hurt?
Go change your clothes.
Shen Jingmo,
when I saw Lu Xu lying in a pool of blood today,
I was actually laughing.
Do you think I'm a devil
or a good person?
It depends on whose perspective.
In my eyes,
you are a good person.
Thank you.
Do you still think I'm a good person now?
I said
those people
don't deserve you to stain your hands.
Even if you really take me as a stepping stone,
I'm also willing to do it.
If the place you're going to is endless darkness,
I'm willing to accompany you
to the endless darkness.
But we just...
Jenny, what are you going to do?
Ah.
Don't struggle anymore.
This is a water-soluble tie.
If it falls into the river,
it will dissolve naturally in two hours.
Jenny,
Are you crazy?
Crazy?
I am crazy.
And you made me crazy.
Since I accidentally got that file,
I have become a pawn on your chessboard.
You are sure that I dare not confront Annie,
and can only present the evidence to the Young Master.
And all of this was carefully planned by you.
You drugged Lu Qianqian's water in advance.
Props, sets, and actors.
You're really a thoughtful director.
Then you just wait for the Young Master to see the materials
and impulsively confront you,
falling into your trap,
and killing the Lu family through me.
You're really something, Jiang Li.
When you do what I want,
you will also get
what you want.
Now,
it's my turn to set the rules of the game.
You...
Ah.
You're really a devil.
You even used the bitter scheme.
You planned to anger Zhou Jian
and let him vent his resentment accumulated over the years
to cripple the Young Master.
If he does anything to hurt me,
will you protect me?
But a car accident almost killed him.
Maybe that's more to your liking.
After all, he is in the ICU,
so he can't expose your true colors.
Your revenge is not just for your sister.
Your target is not just Zhou Jian and Lu Qianqian.
20 years ago,
Your parents died in the Su family's factory fire.
And now,
you want the entire Lu family to be buried with them.
Jenny,
do you believe in karma?
I do.
That's why I'll pay with my life.
If you kill me today,
it's also the cause and effect.
Are you willing to take the consequences?
How's it going?
Have you found her?
We haven't found Jiang Li yet.
There's no one at home,
and her phone is off.
I see.
Let me know as soon as you have any updates.
Okay.
It's no use drinking here.
Maybe she just wants to be alone.
She'll be back soon.
Jiang Li has been missing for 36 hours.
There are 48 hours left until the press conference.
What's wrong?
My mom...
She's coming back.
It's time to take a bow.
My Black Queen,
the princess from the fairy tale,
is about to make a dazzling entrance.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Dear.
Oh my.
Long time no see.
You look stunning today.
Go inside.
Okay.
Hello?
This is...
What's wrong, honey?
The guests are almost all here.
Why don't you get changed?
It's the police.
They found Jiang Li's car in the wild.
She might be in trouble.
I'll be right back.
[People who worship money]
[will eventually become hungry wolves.]
It would be better if she were dead.
[When they greedily devour their own kind,]
[they forget they were once humans who walked on two legs.]
[The brighter the glow of a wealthy family,]
[the deeper the shadow on the other side.]
[But it doesn't matter.]
[I am the darkness that comes to devour]
[those false glows.]
The rose you crowned me with has long withered into thorns.
I planted thorns in the ruins you burned.
Tonight,
they will climb your sturdy castle
and carve your testimony of sins on every brick.
The trending topic is blowing up.
The rich in-law cheated on his brother's fiancée.
Even TV dramas wouldn't dare to film such a plot.
But the Golden Silk Group's
Dark Fairy Tale Series Fashion Show is approaching.
But the Lu Family exposed a shocking scandal.
Look, Lu Qianqian is coming out.
Mr. Lu.
Hasn't Jiang Li disappeared?
How could she appear again?
Is this the first time you've learned about your husband's infidelity?
Does Annie know about this?
Will this affect the company's listing?
When will Annie come back?
Mr. Lu.
The live streaming room has reached a climax at this moment.
Now, a guest is about to appear.
Who do you think it will be?
That's right.
It's our female lead,
Miss Lu,
Lu Qianqian.
It's you?
Where's Jiang Li?
Where is she?